JIAYI ZHANG

J +86 18831933368 **≥** 2020201387@ruc.edu.cn

Renmin University of China, Zhongguancun Street, Haidian, Beijing, 100872, CHINA

Personal Statement __

I am a senior student from the School of Information, Renmin University of China, possessing execellent engineering capabilities and rich research experiences. I am actively seeking a phd position for my **next 4 year**. My research interests include studies related to **LLM-Based Agent**, such as multi-agent systems, embodied agents in the digital world, llm-based-agent for data science, etc. I look forward to the prospect of contributing to school's research!

EDUCATION ___

Renmin University of China

Bachelor, School of Information

Beijing, China 2020.9 - 2024.7

WORKING MANUSCRIPTS _

- 1. **Jiayi Zhang**, Yihan Zhao, Zeping Chen, Ming He. **MobileExperts: A Dynamic Embodied Agent Team In Mobile Devices**, NIPS 2024 Under Preparation.
- 2. Sirui Hong, Yizhang Lin, Bangbang Liu, Binhao Wu, Danyang Li, Jiaqi Chen, **Jiayi Zhang**, Jinlin Wang, Lingyao Zhang, Mingchen Zhuge, Taicheng Guo, Tuo Zhou, Wei Tao, Wenyi Wang, Xiangru Tang, Xiangtao Lu, Xinbing Liang, Yaying Fei, Yuheng Cheng, Zongze Xu, Chenglin Wu, Li Zhang, Min Yang, Xiawu Zheng. **Data Interpreter:** An LLM Agent For Data Science, *Arxiv Preprint*.

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE ___

RUC Smart Society Governance and Engineering Laboratory

Beijing, China

Research Intern | Supervisor: Keman Huang, Jilei Zhou

Apr. 2022 - Present

Topic: LLM-Based MultiAgent System for Social Simulation ; Complex Network

DeepWisdom Shenzhen, China (Online)

Research Intern | Supervisor: Chenlin Wu

Sep. 2023 - Present

Topic: LLM-Based MultiAgent System for Problem-Solving; LLM-Based Agent for Data Science; Foundation Agent

AI Laboratory at Lenovo Research

Beijing, China

Research Intern | Supervisor: Ming He

Dec. 2023 - Present

Topic: Embodied Agent (PC / Mobile Environment); Vision Language Model

INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE _

Algorithm Intern | Zhipu AI

Aug. 2023 - Dec. 2023

- Developed a 2D avatar streaming system based on SadTalker and ChatGLM, enabling interactions within 5 seconds.
- Designed Chat2Way for TTS from LLM-texts; created Wav2Stream for 2D avatar streaming.

Algorithm Intern | Changyou.com (CYOU)

Jul. 2023 - Aug. 2023

- Assisted in building Changyou's internal QA platform using LangChain-chatchat.
- Enhanced LangChain's Loader, enabling diverse file handling and reducing LLM's knowledge hallucinations.

PROFESSIONAL PROJECTS __

Prompt Navigator - Baidu & FounderPark AGI Hackacthon

Dec. 2023

Second Place Award

- I led a team to develop this open-source tool in a two-day hackathon, and won the second prize (2/201).
- Prompt Navigator can automatically optimize and evaluate Prompts, and realize automation in generalized performance tests. Three strategies COT, Contrastive, and Difficulty under Zero shot & few shot have been implemented.

Sep. 2023

2 out of 4 awards

- As a team member, I participated in the development of AWS Master, completed the development of the interface and vector retrieval part, and won two awards in this hackathon event.
- AWSMaster can parse the code uploaded by users, automatically determine the project type, and provide interactive voice or text guidance for AWS server deployment.

MetaGPT - Mini hackathon

Best Contributor

- I participated in MetaGPT team's replicated Multi-environment Mini Hackathon, throughout which I utilized the MetaGPT's framework to successfully replicate Stanford Town within a three-week period.
- Implement memory and retrieval mechanism for Agent; improve the Agent Reflect process; improve and test the Sandbox localization mechanism; implement memory and personality Loader tools.

LEADERSHIP & ACTIVITY __

• RUC 36th Student Union Committee | Member

Jun. 2023 - Present

• RUC 45th School of Information Student Union | Chairman

Apr. 2023 - Mar. 2024

• RUC 1th Mingli Academy Student Union | Chairman

Sep. 2022 - Jul. 2023

• RUC 1th E-sports competition | Chief Director

Mar. 2023

AWARDS ____

• The First Class Academic Progress Scholarship. Renmin University of China.	2022
• The First Class Social Work and Leadership Scholarship Renmin University of China.	2022
• The First Class Outstanding Student Leadership Scholarship. Renmin University of China.	2023

• Merit Student Award. Renmin University of China.

2023

SKILLS ___

- Programming Frameworks: Python, C, SQL, Vue, Django, Flask, FastAPI, Gradio, Streamlit, Langchain, Pytorch
- Commonly Used Tools: Linux, Git, Conda, Postman, Drawio, Obsidian, Zotero, Google Scholar, Overleaf
- Language: IELTS 6.5